{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Select the statement that best describes the parity method of error detection:", "opta": "Parity checking is best suited for detecting double-bit errors that occur during the transmission of codes from one location to another.", "optb": "Parity checking is not suitable for detecting single-bit errors in transmitted codes.", "optc": "Parity checking is best suited for detecting single-bit errors in transmitted codes.", "optd": "Parity checking is capable of detecting and correcting errors in transmitted codes.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A logic circuit that provides a HIGH output for both inputs HIGH or both inputs LOW is a(n):", "opta": "Ex-NOR gate", "optb": "OR gate", "optc": "Ex-OR gate", "optd": "NAND gate", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A logic circuit that provides a HIGH output if one input or the other input, but not both, is HIGH, is a(n):", "opta": "Ex-NOR gate", "optb": "OR gate", "optc": "Ex-OR gate", "optd": "NAND gate", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Identify the type of gate below from the equation", "opta": "Ex-NOR gate", "optb": "OR gate", "optc": "Ex-OR gate", "optd": "NAND gate", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How is odd parity generated differently from even parity?", "opta": "The first output is inverted.", "optb": "The last output is inverted.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Parity systems are defined as either________ or ________ and will add an extra ________ to the digital information being transmitted.", "opta": "positive, negative, byte", "optb": "odd, even, bit", "optc": "upper, lower, digit", "optd": "on, off, decimal", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which type of gate can be used to add two bits?", "opta": "Ex-OR", "optb": "Ex-NOR", "optc": "Ex-NAND", "optd": "NOR", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Why is an exclusive-NOR gate also called an equality gate?", "opta": "The output is false if the inputs are equal.", "optb": "The output is true if the inputs are opposite.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Show from the truth table how an exclusive-OR gate can be used to invert the data on one input if the other input is a special control function.", "opta": "Using A as the control, when A = 0, X is the same as B. When A = 1, X is the same as B.", "optb": "Using A as the control, when A = 0, X is the same as B. When A = 1, X is the inverse of B.", "optc": "Using A as the control, when A = 0, X is the inverse of B. When A = 1, X is the same as B.", "optd": "Using A as the control, when A = 0, X is the inverse of B. When A = 1, X is the inverse of B.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Determine odd parity for each of the following data words: 1011101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a011110111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01001101", "opta": "P = 1, P = 1, P = 0", "optb": "P = 0, P = 0, P = 0", "optc": "P = 1, P = 1, P = 1", "optd": "P = 0, P = 0, P = 1", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Ex-NOR is sometimes called the ________.", "opta": "parity gate", "optb": "equality gate", "optc": "inverted OR", "optd": "parity gate or the equality gate", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}